export const quotes = [
    "In a world of screens, make mindful choices, with ADD, hear your inner voices.",
    "In the realm of digital haste, ADD is your peaceful space.",
    "Limit the virtual, embrace the actual.",
    "Screen break, soul's awake.",
    "Release the virtual hold, discover your inner gold.",
    "Step back from the screen, let your spirit be seen.",
    "Break the online chain, find peace again.",
    "Anuvrat Digital Detox, a new life unboxed.",
    "Free your mind, leave the screen behind.",
    "In a world full of digital distractions, dining should be a time for human connection.",
    "Savor the flavors, not the screen.",
    "In the online world, we often get lost. Unplug for a while, it's worth the cost.",
    "Virtual reality can be quite a show, but real life's where the best stories flow.",
    "Charging your phone, but what about you? Take time for yourself, it's long overdue.",
    "Want to find peace of mind? ADD is the chance to unplug and unwind.",
    "Overuse it, and you might just lose it.",
    "Swipe and click, life's moments slip.",
    "Screens may entertain, but is that your aim?",
    "Overuse the device, and you'll pay the price.",
    "Swipe and scroll but don't lose control.",
    "Swipe and tap, who cares about a real-life map?",
    "Overuse the device, it's a shortcut to paradise.",
    "Reality is a bore, who needs it anymore?",
    "Sarcasm aside, put the device aside.",
    "Screen's addiction is a breeze, it will bring you to your knees.",
    "Digital spell, reality farewell.",
    "Swipe, click, we're losing our tick.",
    "Tech-free days, pave the disturbing ways.",
    "Real world is there, don't forget to care.",
    "For a clearer mind, leave devices behind.",
    "Put devices to rest, refresh your best.",
    "Screens out of sight, reclaim your inner light.",
    "Let screens take a break, for your own sake.",
    "Unplug and detach, find your natural match.",
    "Screen is a charm, beware of its harm.",
    "Ditch the tweets, savor real-life treats.",
    "Text less, live more, on the ADD floor.",
    "Unplug, recharge, your soul needs a massage.",
    "Digital detox, the real life connect rocks.",
    "Swipe right on nature, it's a great feature.",
    "Keyboard click of Nature's trick - take your pick.",
    "Break the tech spell, live life incredibly well.",
    "Logout, explore, life is an open door.",
    "Shut the screen, unlock your dream.",
  ];
  
  export const riddles = [
    {
      question: "I'm a constant companion in your hand, but when you need a break, I must be banned. What am I?",
      answer: "Your smartphone.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a place where you scroll, like, and tweet, but stepping away from me can make your life sweet. What am I?",
      answer: "Social media.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a device that offers endless connection, but sometimes, it's wise to seek disconnection. What am I?",
      answer: "A computer or tablet.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a source of information and news, yet turning me off can give you the blues. What am I?",
      answer: "The internet.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a digital pastime, a game or a show, but taking a break from me can help you grow. What am I?",
      answer: "Streaming services.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm where photos and stories come to play, but remember to put me down and enjoy the day. What am I?",
      answer: "Instagram.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a social app with a picture-perfect theme, but real life's the canvas of your dream. What am I?",
      answer: "Instagram.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a world of posts and hashtags, it's true, but unplugging from me can give you a better view. What am I?",
      answer: "Instagram.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm where tweets fly and trends take flight, but to unwind, you might want to unplug from this site. What am I?",
      answer: "Twitter.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm the platform for thoughts in 280 characters or less, but sometimes, it's good to escape the digital mess. What am I?",
      answer: "Twitter.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a place for follows, retweets, and news, yet stepping away from me can help cure the blues. What am I?",
      answer: "Twitter.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a platform with videos, diverse and vast, but sometimes, it's good to take a break and make moments last. What am I?",
      answer: "YouTube.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm where creators share their talents and art, but it's essential to unplug and play your own part. What am I?",
      answer: "YouTube.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a site with vlogs, tutorials, and song covers too, yet a digital detox can bring a fresh view. What am I?",
      answer: "YouTube.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm known for subscribers and video streams, but turning me off can lead to pleasant dreams. What am I?",
      answer: "YouTube.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm where you can binge on content for hours, but remember, life's a stage where you hold the powers. What am I?",
      answer: "YouTube.",
    },
    {
      question: "I connect the world with clicks and bytes, yet my manufacturing can lead to environmental fights. What am I?",
      answer: "The internet and digital technology.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm the cloud, where data's stored with ease, yet my servers consume energy that impacts the trees. What am I?",
      answer: "Cloud computing.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm all about groups, chats, and connections, but pausing for a while can reduce life's tensions. What am I?",
      answer: "WhatsApp.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm where conversations and media thrive, but sometimes, it's good to unplug and feel alive. What am I?",
      answer: "WhatsApp.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a digital mind that learns and predicts, but should we use me for all, or is there a risk? What am I?",
      answer: "Artificial Intelligence.",
    },
    {
      question: "I can process data with speed and precision, but should we rely on me without decision? What am I?",
      answer: "Artificial Intelligence.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm the future of technology, that's clear, but using me ethically is something we should hold dear. What am I?",
      answer: "Artificial Intelligence.",
    },
    {
      question: "I can analyze and adapt, it's true, but humans must guide what I should do. What am I?",
      answer: "Artificial Intelligence.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a digital show that you can't resist, but sometimes, a break from me will bring bliss. What am I?",
      answer: "A web series.",
    },
    {
      question: "I bring stories to screens both big and small, but remember to unplug and enjoy life's call. What am I?",
      answer: "A web series.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm where drama and laughter are at their best, yet taking a pause from me can be a life's zest. What am I?",
      answer: "A web series.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm a series you binge-watch night and day, but don't forget to step outside and play. What am I?",
      answer: "A web series.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm the shield against online threats so vast, but my strength depends on how long I'll last. What am I?",
      answer: "Cybersecurity.",
    },
    {
      question: "I guard your information from breaches and hacks, but without regular updates, I might have cracks. What am I?",
      answer: "Cybersecurity.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm the lock on the digital door, a defender of the online war, but human actions are what I implore. What am I?",
      answer: "Cybersecurity.",
    },
    {
      question: "I'm all about passwords, firewalls, and encryption, but neglecting me can lead to data's extinction. What am I?",
      answer: "Cybersecurity.",
    },
  ];

export const didYouKnowFacts = [
    "Ed Sheeran uses the phone for only 1.5 hours a day.",
    "Amir Khan has taken a break from social media.",
    "Barack Obama enjoys mental well-being rather than using the phone.",
    "Tom Holland (Spider-Man) has taken a digital detox for years.",
    "Dhoni does not have a phone but uses it only to set an alarm at night.",
    "Neerja Birla has a rule that no smartphones are allowed during dinner.",
    "Justin Bieber doesn't have a cell phone but uses an iPad only to communicate.",
    "Anand Mahindra was impressed by a Maharashtrian village that practices daily digital detox.",
    "Bill Gates didn't give his kids a cell phone until they were fourteen.",
    "Akshay Kumar is away from his mobile phones most of the time and uses it only when it is urgent.",
    "Emma Watson, actress: 'I think it's important for everyone to take a break from their devices from time to time. It's good for your mental and physical health.'",
    "Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft: 'I've found that I'm more creative and productive when I'm not constantly checking my phone.'",
    "75% of adolescents who use their phones at bedtime have trouble sleeping. (Source: National Sleep Foundation)",
    "75% of people say they're more stressed when they're constantly checking their phones: RescueTime, 'The State of Work Distraction' (2022)",
    "Selena Gomez, singer, and actress: 'I'm not saying you have to give up your phone forever, but taking a digital detox every now and then is a great way to recharge and reconnect with yourself.'",
    "E-waste is the fastest-growing waste stream in the world. (Source: United Nations Environment Programme, 'Global E-Waste Monitor 2022')",
    "Misinformation on social media spreads six times faster than true information. (Source: Massachusetts Institute of Technology)",
    "67% of people who use digital devices regularly experience eye strain. (Source: American Academy of Ophthalmology)",
    "72% of people who use digital devices regularly experience neck or back pain. (Source: Mayo Clinic)",
    "Carrie Underwood, singer, logs off her phone when she is with her parents.",
    "Paul Gottsegan, CMO of Mindtree, uses meetings as an opportunity to digitally detox, showing up most times with no phones or laptops.",
    "Kanye West, singer, wrote about digital detox which created 90,000 likes, and 32,000 people had retrieved it.",
    "Kendall Jenner appreciates people logging off phones.",
    "Britney Spears hates using social digital apps.",
    "Karanvir Bohra has prioritized 'digital upwas'.",
    "Sangli, Maharashtra, India, has announced that T.V and phones should be off from 7 pm to 8:30 pm."
  ];


export const dosAndDonts = [
    "Not scrolling more than 15 minutes.",
    "No gossip talks on call.",
    "No phone in the washroom.",
    "No electronic gadgets while having meals.",
    "15 minutes of observing your surroundings.",
    "One-time analysis of the usage of apps.",
    "No music while working.",
    "No multi-tasking.",
    "No gambling.",
    "No toxic content consumption.",
    "10 minutes of laughter with your loved ones.",
    "15 minutes of outdoor activities.",
    "10 minutes spending time in nature.",
    "15 minutes of family time.",
    "10 minutes of self-introspection.",
    "10 minutes of reading.",
    "No usage of Alexa or similar devices.",
    "Make your screen black & white.",
    "Check phone at every 30 minutes interval.",
    "2 hours of fasting while awake.",
    "No OTT consumption.",
    "No online food delivery.",
    "No online shopping.",
    "Skip one social media app.",
    "Not watching live broadcasting of sports.",
    "5 minutes of meditation.",
    "5 minutes of focused deep breathing.",
    "10 minutes of yoga.",
    "10 minutes of physical exercise.",
    "Promote & mentor digital detox activity to 3 people.",
    "5 minutes of chanting.",
    "No social updates, viz: Story, Status, Post.",
    "15 minutes of brainstorming.",
    "No movie.",
    "No web series.",
    "No TV.",
    "No news.",
    "Limit screen-time till hours.",
    "Consume career growth content for 15 minutes.",
    "Do not stalk anyone else.",
    "30 minutes communication in person.",
    "Don't make unnecessary reels/videos/photos.",
    "Don't touch the mobile for 1 hour while conscious.",
    "Don't use incognito or private browsing.",
    "Schedule your day in creative activities.",
    "Quitting any 1 social media platform (WhatsApp, Instagram, Snapchat).",
    "Tyaag of Insta for 2 (active) hours.",
    "Only half an hour gaming.",
    "Restraint from the digital world after 10 pm.",
    "Restraint from the digital world till 2 hours of waking up.",
    "Restraint from the digital world while eating.",
    "No shorts & reels for a day.",
    "Restraint from the digital world while walking.",
    "Restraint from movies (in a given time span).",
    "Restraint from series (in a given time span).",
    "Complete digital fast for half a day.",
    "Do not post pics the day it was clicked.",
    "Checking messages only at some specific times (e.g., 6 am, 10 am, 2 pm, 6 pm, 10 pm).",
    "One hour in a day you should daily restraint from any digital world.",
    "Not to use digital staff for more than 20 minutes at a stretch.",
    "Uninstall gaming apps every night.",
    "Turn off notifications of all messaging apps.",
    "Having a deliberate 20 minutes outing without a phone.",
    "Charge gadgets (such as phone, laptop, AirPods, earphones, etc) only once a day.",
    "Switch off phones/laptop while studying or silent all sorts of notifications.",
    "Quitting online shopping for a given period of time.",
    "Restraint from using mobile while conversing with someone (at least till 5 minutes).",
    "I will constantly observe my screentime & write it down.",
    "Limit time of every app you use to 1 hour.",
    "Use mobile only for the double of the time you do any physical outdoor activity.",
    "Learn first aid skills.",
    "15 minutes of healthy debate.",
    "Spontaneous JAM (Just A Minute) speaking.",
    "Crack a joke.",
    "Ask 3 riddles.",
    "Borrow a self-help book.",
    "Talk to helping hands.",
    "Give a smile & compliment others.",
    "Note down your dreams.",
    "Maintain a wish list (5–6 dreams).",
    "Write a letter to your future (100 words).",
    "Appreciate yourself for 5 minutes.",
    "Prepare a schedule for tomorrow.",
    "Storytelling with words for 5 minutes.",
    "Fix a routine for one month.",
    "Practice gratitude for 8 minutes.",
    "Affirmative sentence for 3 minutes (e.g., I am ever growing & glowing, I am peaceful, powerful & purposeful).",
    "Solving a quiz/asking G.K questions.",
    "Sleep till 10 o'clock.",
    "Wake up at 7 o'clock.",
    "Doing household chores.",
    "Practice forgiveness (forget a lot, forgetting a lot).",
    "20 minutes family activity.",
    "10 minutes Pranayama.",
    "Reading 1 story."
  ];

  export const quizQnA = [
    {
      question: "What percentage of the global population owns a smartphone in 2022?",
      options: ["30%", "50%", "70%", "90%"],
      answer: "70%",
    },
    {
      question: "What percentage of households in developed nations have multiple digital devices?",
      options: ["40%", "60%", "80%", "95%"],
      answer: "80%",
    },
    {
      question: "How many connected devices are estimated to be in use worldwide by the year 2025?",
      options: ["10 billion", "20 billion", "30 billion", "50 billion"],
      answer: "20 billion",
    },
    {
      question: "What percentage of internet traffic is estimated to come from mobile devices in recent years?",
      options: ["20%", "40%", "60%", "80%"],
      answer: "80%",
    },
    {
      question: "What percentage of cyberattacks target small businesses annually?",
      options: ["10%", "25%", "43%", "70%"],
      answer: "70%",
    },
    {
      question: "How many data records were exposed in the top 5 data breaches of all time as of 2022?",
      options: ["500 million", "1 billion", "3 billion", "7 billion"],
      answer: "3 billion",
    },
    {
      question: "What health issue jumps by 27% in eighth-graders who frequently use social media?",
      options: ["Anxiety", "Internet addiction", "Depression", "Insomnia"],
      answer: "Depression",
    },
    {
      question: "Which tech leader limited his kids' use of the newly-released iPad?",
      options: ["Bill Gates", "Steve Jobs", "Mark Zuckerberg", "Elon Musk"],
      answer: "Steve Jobs",
    },
    {
      question: "What did Elon Musk say about artificial intelligence?",
      options: [
        "It will bring about the end of the world.",
        "We are summoning the demon.",
        "It has no impact on human existence.",
        "It will revolutionize the future positively."
      ],
      answer: "We are summoning the demon.",
    },
    {
      question: "What percentage of accidents involving cars are caused by cell phone use, as per the provided data?",
      options: ["50%", "26%", "70%", "99%"],
      answer: "26%",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the reported average global screen time in 2023?",
      options: ["8 hours and 30 minutes", "6 hours and 58 minutes", "5 hours and 45 minutes", "10 hours and 20 minutes"],
      answer: "6 hours and 58 minutes",
    },
    {
      question: "What percentage of dark web listings are related to criminal activity?",
      options: ["87%", "76%", "68%", "82%"],
      answer: "87%",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the reported health effects of proximity to radiation towers?",
      options: [
        "Cancer, headache, insomnia, and fatigue",
        "ADHD, anxiety, and depression",
        "Alcohol abuse and internet addiction",
        "Social media addiction and depression"
      ],
      answer: "Cancer, headache, insomnia, and fatigue",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the estimated number of virtual and augmented reality users expected by 2030?",
      options: ["50 million", "1 billion", "5 billion", "90 million"],
      answer: "1 billion",
    },
    {
      question: "In which documentary was it suggested that social media nurtures addiction to maximize profit?",
      options: ["The Great Hack", "Social Dilemma", "The Facebook Dilemma", "Social Addiction"],
      answer: "Social Dilemma",
    },
    {
      question: "What action did former Microsoft CEO Bill Gates take concerning his children's technology usage?",
      options: [
        "He encouraged unlimited screen time",
        "He set strict limitations on screen time",
        "He provided iPads to his children",
        "He allowed cell phones from a young age"
      ],
      answer: "He set strict limitations on screen time",
    },
    {
      question: "How many personal data of Facebook users were leaked in the 'Great Hack' incident?",
      options: ["50 million", "100 million", "10 million", "200 million"],
      answer: "50 million",
    },
    {
      question: "According to recent studies, what percentage of fake news stories spreads quicker than accurate news on social media platforms?",
      options: ["25%", "50%", "75%", "100%"],
      answer: "50%",
    },
    {
      question: "How much financial loss is estimated due to misinformation and fake news annually, globally?",
      options: ["$1 million", "$50 million", "$78 billion", "$100 billion"],
      answer: "$100 billion",
    },
  ];
  
  

  